{
    "subject": "resource/3_Doors_Down",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "3 Doors Down",
    "human_readable": "The name of 3 Doors Down is 3 Doors Down.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9488222002983093,
            "question": "Is the name of the band 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9347103834152222,
            "question": "Who are 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9157707095146179,
            "question": "What is the name of the band 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8871622681617737,
            "question": "Is '3 Doors Down' a common band name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8567718863487244,
            "question": "What musical group is known as 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8019313812255859,
            "question": "Do they call themselves 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7735480070114136,
            "question": "Can you name any popular songs by 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.707808792591095,
            "question": "How would you describe the band 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6386739611625671,
            "question": "What genre of music is typically associated with 3 Doors Down?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03239245340228081,
            "question": "What name is associated with the band?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of 3 Doors Down is 3 Doors Down.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9314_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is typically associated with 3 Doors Down?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9314_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the band 3 Doors Down?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9314_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any popular songs by 3 Doors Down?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9314_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9314_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents provided contain information about 3 Doors Down, and specifically mention their band name as \"3 Doors Down\". This confirms that the statement is true according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided clearly states that the band's name \"3 Doors Down\" was inspired by their location in relation to a venue where they used to practice, signifying their humble beginnings. This supports the statement that the name of the band is indeed 3 Doors Down."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}